<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="error_999">Что-то пошло не так. Повторите запрос позднее.</string>
    <string name="http_no_internet">Нет соединения с сетью</string>

    <!-- 0.XX-->
    <string name="error_0_101">This error occurs if the client cannot connect to the API.</string>
    <string name="error_0_102">This error occurs if the client tries to connect to the API using a protocol different from the HTTPS one.</string>

    <!-- 1.XX-->
    <string name="error_1_0">Provider authorization was completed successfully.</string>
    <string name="error_1_101">Provider authorization failed because provider authorization token is not available.</string>
    <string name="error_1_102">Provider authorization failed because the provider was blocked. Provider cannot use the system.</string>
    <string name="error_1_103">Provider authorization failed because the format of the entered provider authorization token is invalid.</string>
    <string name="error_1_104">The operation requires provider authorization. You must authorize a provider before proceeding with the operation.
    </string>

    <!-- 7.XX-->
    <string name="error_7_101">This error occurs if a user requests a document that is not available
        or was not uploaded by them, for example, if the requested document belongs to another user.
    </string>
    <string name="error_7_102">This error occurs if a user was requested to upload verification
        documents, but did not upload any of them (for example, the scanned copy of their passport)
        and did not select the Documents sent by email option.
    </string>
    <!-- 2.XX-->
    <string name="error_2_0">User was authorized by their email address.</string>
    <string name="error_2_1">User was authorized by their mobile phone number.</string>
    <string name="error_2_2">User was authorized by their token.</string>
    <string name="error_2_101">User authorization failed because the provided password is invalid.
    </string>
    <string name="error_2_102">User authorization failed because the credentials required for
        authorization were provided in the wrong format.
    </string>
    <string name="error_2_103">User authorization failed because the user with the specified
        credentials was not registered in the system.
    </string>
    <string name="error_2_104">User authorization failed because the mobile phone number specified
        during authorization
        belongs to more than one user.
    </string>
    <string name="error_2_105">User authorization failed because their account is blocked.</string>
    <string name="error_2_106">User authorization failed because the provided authorization token
        was not found.
    </string>
    <string name="error_2_107">User authorization failed because the provided authorization token is
        no longer active and cannot be used.
    </string>
    <string name="error_2_108">User is not authorized.</string>

    <!-- 3.XX-->
    <string name="error_3_101">This error occurs if a required parameter is missing from the request.</string>
    <string name="error_3_102">This error occurs if the available provider/user authorization header is invalid.</string>
    <string name="error_3_103">The requested operation cannot be performed because it is prohibited by the current workflow. For example, if a user that has a live (not closed) loan tries to apply for another one, the GeneralValidation: WorkflowValidationError occurs, because users can have only one live loan.</string>
    <string name="error_3_104">   This error occurs if a user did not fill in all required fields or entered data is invalid and does not meet field requirements.</string>

    <!-- 4.XX-->
    <string name="error_4_101">Credit card was not found.</string>
    <string name="error_4_102">User\'s credit card verification was completed successfully. This message is displayed to inform about successful card validation when adding a card, performing payment with 3D Secure, etc.</string>
    <string name="error_4_103">The credit card cannot be set as a primary card because it does not belong to the user who is trying to perform this operation.</string>
    <string name="error_4_104">The credit card cannot be selected as a primary card.</string>
    <string name="error_4_105">Internal service problem occurred. Please contact MoneyVeo.</string>
    <string name="error_4_106">Error on adding a credit card. The card was not added to the user\'s account.</string>
    <string name="error_4_107">Payment was not found. This message identifies the payment status.</string>
    <string name="error_4_108">The payment was declined by an external payment system.</string>
    <string name="error_4_109">The number of attempts to enter the amount of money blocked during card verification was exceeded.</string>
    <string name="error_4_110">The entered amount of money blocked during card verification is invalid.</string>

    <!-- 5.XX-->
    <string name="error_5_101">User registration failed because such user already exists.</string>
    <string name="error_5_102">Registration of the user account was completed successfully.</string>

    <!-- 6.XX-->

    <string name="error_6_0">The provided promo code is valid and has been activated successfully.</string>
    <string name="error_6_1"> The provided promo code is invalid and cannot be used.</string>
    <string name="error_6_2">This error occurs if a user tries to apply personalized promo code while they are not authorized in the system.</string>
    <string name="error_6_3">The provided promo code has expired and cannot be used</string>

</resources>